Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching!
Arena!
Hey there!
Alina!
Yoo-hoo!
There's music playing that only we can hear.
It's playing.
Yes, everyone!
Good evening!
We are,
We are the FB middle school!
What kind of greeting?
Not much. We're just us.
I, Yamanashiko Nakayama, will be your host today.
Nakayama, how long have you been here?
It's been January.
How many months has it been?
I haven't seen you for about 2 months.
I don't know. But I was on.
You were?
Yes, I was.
I saw it.
I haven't been on since January.
And there are two more today.
Please introduce yourself!
Did you say you're Riko Nakayama?
I think I said Riko Nakayama.
I am Riko Nakayama.
I am Hino Kashiwagi. Please introduce yourself.
Yes, I am Cocona Sakurai.
Pleased to meet you.
Well, let's begin!
Let's go! Shrimp addiction!
The Delightful and Fumfumfun Showroom!
Yes, thank you very much for watching the 48th Ebiichu's Delightful and Fun-filled Showroom today.
Thank you very much.
Yes, the EBICHU's Delightful and FUN FUN FUN Showroom is the sister show of our sister show, Ukka's Showroom.
Yes, good evening.
Yes, good evening, good evening everyone.
Good evening.
I'm here to play. I made it in time. Good, good, good.
I'm glad.
Riko said it's been a while.
That's right.
It says it's been a while.
It's been a while.
So, let's announce the ranking. May I have a word?
It's okay, right?
Let's announce the rankings.
You want to see it?
Luck.
Starting in fifth place.
Okay, I'm in.
You want to go out?
Fifth place, Mucha at Family.
Thank you very much.
Fourth place, Mayuge-san. Thank you very much.
Third place, Shackelpode. Thank you very much.
No.2, Mr. Endo. Thank you very much.
And first place, Mr. Yutsuzu. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
You can get the original avatar of Ebichu Showroom by registering to our showroom,
You can get it by giving a gift either for free or for a fee.
Yes.
Almost, Kao-chan wrote this original avatar.
It's all neatly arranged, isn't it?
She's a good girl.
Be nice. Please, everyone.
By all means.
And if you click on the Twitter symbol at the bottom of the screen,
You can spread the word about this distribution on Twitter.
Your cooperation.
Yes. So, this is the time to spread the word.
To get as many people as possible to see this distribution,
I'm going to tweet an announcement on Twitter,
Please tweet about it.
Now, let's have a picture taken.
And Mr. Money Car.
Anybody here?
Oh, there he is.
Two pictures.
Like this.
One.
One card.
One, two, three.
Good morning.
Even though you're wearing a mask,
Are you smiling through the mask?
What?
Are you laughing?
Good morning.
Youth Zombie is the song of the summer.
What's this?
There it is. There it is.
Something's here.
Who is it?Who is this?
Hi, I'm Yukkari.
This is Mr. Yukari.
It's Mr. Yukari.
You were doing it just now, right?
You waved your hand and she waved back even though we were in the middle of a live streaming.
Really?
He was watching us.
He came on Monday.
Really? Thank you.
I knew it. This weekend.
I'm a family girl with a summer family commitment,
I'm here to support them.
I'm glad.
What are you gonna do?
I'll tell you. Moa-chan.
Kashiwagi-san.
I'm rooting for you, Famire.
And I like your singing voice.
Thank you very much. I will try my best.
I'm glad.
It's kind of perfect.
There are a lot of them.
Do you have any?
Yes, I have a release.
This is a sudden announcement.
Uka will be making her major label debut on November 16th with Teichika Entertainment.
Thank you very much.
So, we are going to make our first major album,
The song "VIVA LA VIDA" has been distributed from 0:00 today,
Please listen to it. Please listen to it.
Please listen to it.
I said OK, so go home now.
Thank you very much.
Next time, please listen to the special.
Please listen to it. All of you.
Good luck.
See you soon.
Good night.
Good work.
I'm sorry. Really.
You didn't return it? You haven't returned it?
I can't pay you back.
I want to show you how much I hate it.
I haven't returned it a few times.
What? That many?
But I know I haven't returned it properly.
I've been telling myself I haven't.
I'm sorry I didn't return it.
Everyone, please listen to today's broadcast.
Please listen to Fuku-chan's song.
Please do.
What did we talk about?
Not yet. We haven't talked about anything.
Take a picture.
We just took a picture.
Well, shall we talk about what's going on?
Status talk.
What is it?
It's a little bit faint,
Bang Bang Meat is now available.
Hashtag Ebichu BBB.
Ebichu is releasing 10 months in a row,
This song is the 5th release.
It's a perfect song for summer.
What do you think of the song?
Do you have a favorite point, like COCONUT?
I, uh...
I stopped.
I like my part.
I think the chorus is the most exciting part,
I think the most exciting part is the chorus part.
I think that part is my favorite part.
It's at the end of the first chorus.
Yeah.
I understand. I especially like it.
What about Hinata?
Well, I don't know.
It's like a groovy feeling or something,
Well, the music itself... Oh, here it comes.
Oh, here it comes.
It's a little bit like Alfalfa.
It's like this.
No, but the music itself has a lot of different genres,
It's been a while since I've heard something like this,
In terms of genres, it's like a portfolio of Ebitu's music.
It's been a while since I've been able to hear a song with hip-hop or metal in it, which is kind of like a portfolio of songs in EBITCHU,
I think it's the kind of music that everyone can raise their hands and have fun with in the summer.
What do you think? Riko.
I don't know. Personally, the recording was really difficult.
It was expensive.
It's really difficult, and there are so many things in it...I don't know, it's not a rap song, but there are all kinds of things in it.
I couldn't keep up with it.
I'm sure.
I wondered what I was doing now.
What am I singing about?
Where am I doing what?
But when I heard the finished product, I felt like I had really become an evichu.
When I first received it, I thought it was something new. I wondered what would happen if I sang this evichu,
But it turned out to be an "ebichu" song.I am now a proper ebichu.
I've become an ebichu, you know.
How did you like it? What did you think?
What did you think?
I can't wait to see the choreography.
Oh.
It's like anything is possible.
So many things.
It's like a feeling of being stuck in a room.
Kaho here, she likes to get tired, doesn't she?
That's for sure.
Phew.
She said it might be her favorite song on the site.
She said the lyrics are good.
The lyrics of the chorus are certainly positive and energetic.
Indeed.
It's kind of like a shout-out.
Some songs make you feel positive.
Indeed.
I think everyone's reaction was great. This time.
Why don't you try singing it at least once?
This is not sung by believers.
It's right here.
Listen to the high pitch.
Sing it.
I like the metal part.
I like it.
Throat tofa.
But it's fun. It's a song. Where will you perform it?
Yes, we will. There are a lot of songs that have been distributed so far that we haven't performed yet.
New future?
Oh, we haven't done it.
Maybe just Zombies.
That was it.
I don't know where I'll see it.
And what are you doing these days, Mihaka?
Well, aside from rehearsing for Famien, I've changed my plans for the 2-man ZEPP tour, which is my 10th anniversary of my major debut, and I've been working on a new tour.
I'm currently working on a 2-man ZEPP tour for Minaka-san, and it's called "After School Rock 'n' Roll",
In July, I had a 2-man live with Mr. Kishida, Mr. Taichi Okazaki, and Angstrom.
Let's start with Kishida-san.
ZEPP Nagoya.
Nagoya.
That was fun.
It was great.
The day before the event, it was actually Super Express, but it was postponed,
So Mr. Kishida was on the first day.
I wonder why.
I wonder.
I am in charge of Mind Yankee.
I was in charge of them,
But when I see them in front of me, I get really scared,
I get really scared.
Scared? I get scared?
I get scared of people.
I feel like I can't say anything. I was very shy.
That's what I felt frustrated about.
More, more.
I wanted to connect with them.
If you go to Kiran Bampaku,
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
Who? Who?
This is where Cocona really comes into its own.
Kiran Bampak.
I'll be able to participate again this year.
Thank you very much.
What's the story with Kiran?
Kiran Bampaku always has 4 members,
We have been able to do it,
So, when we are going to play with Kiran, it's been 8 years?
It's been 8 years?
Wow...
It's been 14 years.
I collaborated with KENKAIBA.
We did it as a collaboration,
And this time...
On our side.
Kiran-san came out,
It had been a long time since I saw him perform live.
It had been a long time since I saw Kiran's live performance,
Of course, I have seen him at Kiran Bampachi
I had seen him at the Kiran Bampaku, but I had never seen him that close up.
I was more scared to go out like this.
I was really enjoying it.
I was having a lot of fun. Doing it.
And, our music.
And arrange it like this.
One Night Carnival Love's Bubba Bar.
You know.
It was such a fun thing to do.
This time it was hosted by Ebichu, right?
So even though we are really grateful that you are going to be there
I'm really grateful,
But you know...it's like that,
I'm really thankful that you are going to participate in this event.
And they sang for us,
I feel like everyone is overflowing with such love.
You know. Really.
Even the choreography is perfect.Even the choreography was perfect.
He told me that he had been wondering about the music until the day before the show.
He was lost until the day before,
And you did it with such a high quality.
I was amazed,
I was really impressed.
I don't know how to return the feelings
I wondered how I could return this feeling to them.
I thought, "How can I return this feeling to them?
We did our best.
Even at Kiran Bampaku,
I think it will be on the 18th of September.
Please come and visit us.
I would appreciate it.
And Mr. Taihisa Okazaki.
Yes.
It was too much fun.
No, it was fun.
Riko was so teasing.
Taiku-san, how to count the stars.
With Tekkun.
He sang "How to count the stars" with Tekkun,
And then..,
Tekkun sang
He said something good about each member,
He said something nice about each member.
What did Shinoko say?
Her singing.
She sings better and better every year.
and that she loves baseball.
She loves baseball.
What did she say about Coconan, too?
I'm a new member, but I've already
established.
They all had great things to say about each one of us.
They all said great things about each other. Serious praise.
I was the last one,
I'm winning.
They didn't even praise me.
She said, "Don't you praise the dog?
I asked him if he was going to praise the dog.
He said, "There's nothing to praise.
All he did was praise Uk.
So I got angry and called him a fat margarine.
I called him a fat margarine.
Every time Riko would use me.
Riko is always used in our house, right?
You mean Mr. Taikoku's, right?
She calls me Fatty Margarine.
It was really fun, wasn't it?
I'm sorry, but I'm not sure if I'm right.
How to count the stars
I heard the B melody is high.
The A melody.
I can't sing it.
B melody is too high.
Because I'm singing it,
I think it's high, but
I didn't pay attention to it,
But when I heard it like that, I thought it was really high.
It is high.
The B melody is higher than the chorus.
I don't know, I don't know.
Sadless, too, together.
Oh, yeah.
Taeui's
Mr. Taeyuki's manager
Matsushita-chan.
We'll fight. Suddenly
We had fun.
It was fun.
Matsushita-chan is a fan of Kaho-chan,
Kaho-chan also likes Matsushita-chan
Kaho-chan likes Matsushita-chan
Kaho-chan also likes Matsushita-chan and takes two-shots with her every time,
I told her at the concert,
I told her at the concert and we took two shots on stage,
It doesn't happen often.
It's very rare.
I couldn't get it, you know,
I couldn't get Matsushita-chan.
It was Sony, after all.
Because it wasn't Sardust.
I was not a Sardust.
He said, "Matsushita-chan is cute.
Manager
Are you in desperate need? I asked.
No, no, no, we have enough.
Yes, we have enough,
I think we have enough.
There are a lot of managers with unique personalities.
You have many managers, don't you?
Yes, they are.
Yes, really.
There are only interesting people.
And,
Next day.
With Mr. Angstrom.
I came out of Tsumanai,I just came out of Tsumanai,
How was it?
Hinano-chan.
Well, I don't know,
I told you at the concert,
Project, it's not often that I get to perform with Hello!
Project.
Project,
Project, and even when I did meet them
Project and even if we did meet, it would be at a festival
Project, and even when we did see each other, it was at a different time during the festival,
we would only pass by each other,
but to see them live like this
It was a rare chance for us to get together
It was a lot of fun,
I think it was a lot of fun, and I really enjoyed the time we spent together,
I like it when stars come out unexpectedly,
I think it was a lot of fun, and I also think it was unexpectedly fun to be together with the stars,
I think it was a lot of fun, and it was also a great opportunity for us to work together,
I think it's important for us to respond to their voices.
I was very happy to be able to respond to their voices this time,
I was also very happy to be able to answer their questions.
You were watching the concert, right?
I watched the show just like a normal person.
I thought it was amazing.
It was really expensive.
I was really high,
I was so scared.
I don't know,
When I was greeted in the morning,
You were all really petite,
Oh, my God!
You are all so thin!
Tiny, tiny, tiny!
On stage, you are amazing,
All are different.
They wear deep heels,
And they can dance so crisply.
It was really cool.
It was amazing.
The groove was really good,
I felt that they were not just ordinary idols.
Angstrom has a lot of individuality,
Each of them has a strong individuality.
Each of you has a strong individuality, and you value it,
I guess,
I think they have an atmosphere similar to that of prawns,
I thought that they had a similar atmosphere to prawns,
We also covered the song,
Tage and Mushi are also queens inside and outside,
Hinata-chan made the dance for us,
Thank you very much.
It was not so bad,
I was just looking at the other people's moves,
I was asked to wake them all up,
I had to shake my head for a long time,
But everyone was watching me,
It went surprisingly fast.
It was really amazing.
I was told to ask Hinata to shake her head,
So I thought you knew the choreography.
I knew the song, but not the choreography,
I wasn't the type to copy everything,
I was wondering what I should do,
The day before, I said, "I'm sorry, I can't open the lesson room now.
I'm sorry, I can't open the lesson room now.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Because, you know, when we did it together, if we couldn't do it,
I thought it would be a total waste of time,
I thought it would be easier to teach the others if I did all the choreography first,
But you're doing it all by yourself.
It's not good.
It's too hard,
I'll do the basic choreography, and then the singing choreography later?
I'll put in the basic choreography, and the choreography for the singers will be done on the spot,
I was going to have the singers do the choreography on the spot with the others,
So I took it as it was,
They're all geniuses.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You guys are geniuses.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
But you know, this time, Angstrom's group was with the leader, Take-chan, and our group was with Yuno, who was absent for a little while,
And Yuno was absent this time,
I'd like to do it again with all the members.
By December.
That's right.
Even if it's after December, it's fine. As long as you call me.
That's right. Even as Kashiwagi Hinata.
A dialogue between the three of us.
I wonder if we can.
We don't want to be alone.
One person there.
Angstrom, Shiritomishua, and Hinata Kashiwagi.
Just put a semantic note there.
I think it's good.
See you all again.See you all soon.
So what's next?
August 22 is Bikki Blanca's.
And on August 23rd, Jyunetsu-san.
There will be a smut live at Zephaneidan.
I wonder what will happen.
I wonder how it will turn out.
BikkiBranca will provide us with different songs.
But I'm really looking forward to seeing how Zephaniah will react.
But I feel that everyone will come when they see you.
Thank you very much.
Everybody grab each other.
I'm coming. Thank you very much.
We have a lot of shows in August.
Pamier is coming soon.
So many shows.
I'm looking forward to it.
Since I gave you another update, I thought I'd ask,
What are you doing these days?
I'm here suddenly.
I'd like to hear your updates on what you've been up to.
If you are students, are you already on summer vacation?
It's certainly the beginning of summer vacation.
It's August, isn't it?
Yes, it's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I heard it's your birthday tomorrow.
Happy birthday!
Return guess.
He's practicing piano.
Please play a song from EBICHU.
Please teach me.
You want to play?
I want to play.
I'm processing fish.
Are you watching me while I'm processing?
Fish are difficult to process.
Have you ever handled fish?
Yes, I have.
You have?
Of course I have.
I'm definitely confused here.
Absolutely.
So, let's say there are three rooms.
I don't know.
You don't know.
I don't get it.
Explain.
You cut off the head and take out the internal organs.
Then you wash the meat here. Then you open it like this.
But you know, I'm sorry. No one knows the right answer.
I don't know if this is the right answer. Is it right?
This is what I'm talking about.
Am I right?
Yes. I'm going to remove the guts.
Number three, what did you just have? Just number three?
Number three.
What kind of food was it?
It was grilled with salt, miso or soy sauce.
Is that right?
I think it's right.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I said I didn't process fish in home economics class.
Slicing, slicing, slicing.
What did you process?
I didn't process anything.
I don't process anything.
Is Ibaraki a junior high school in the camp?
Junior high school.
I handled horse mackerel.
You don't handle it?
I didn't handle it. Home economics class.
You did it in the movie.
Oh, what?
I was processing fish.
Wait a minute. He was processing fish.
That's a very strange and reckless request.
Can you tell me what the process is?
Process?
First of all.
First of all, we need to prepare the fish.
What kind of fish?
First, we prepare the fish.
What did you prepare?
Yellowtail.
I don't know what yellowtail is.
How do you do yellowtail?
You have a head, don't you?
There is a head.
I have a head.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I was a little nervous.
I'm sorry.
And it rang.
You have to open it, so open it like this.
Like this. Like this.
Belly. Stomach.Stomach. Stomach.
Open.
It's got bones, right?
Bones?
You want to take the bones out?
Take the bone.
How about something as simple as that?
Take the bone,
Then you don't know what's inside the yellowtail anymore.
Yellowtail?
We don't remove the entrails.
Where are the entrails?
No?
It's just an abacus. I thought so.
It's not an abacus!
Hey! Abacus!
Wait a minute!
Bri's abacus?
I can't do it.
Riko.
Where are the entrails?
He said it was an abacus to remove the bones.
I did it like this.
Don't make me gut you.
We'll have to gut it.
I'll take out the organs.
I got it.
What are you going to do with it after you take it out?
We'll take the skin off.
What?
Skin?
Don't peel it.
I'm a yellowtail.
I don't know, I don't know.
Oh, this one, I get it, I get it, I get it.
Scale, scale.
That's some kind of scaled fish, isn't it?
Does yellowtail have scales?
I don't know.
What are yellowtails?
Nobody knows.
Even Saki today.
Why did you choose yellowtail?
I don't know. I just had some yellowtail sashimi.
No, you didn't.
I ate it.
I didn't just eat sashimi.
Sorry, sorry.
Riko, what are you going to cut?
Are you still going to do it?
One more time.
Riko is going to have to do it too.
I have to cook it.
Yellowtail is big. It's too big.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
What? What was that?
I was listening to everyone's status reports... and I heard you're selling fish.
30,000?
30,000.
I went to Sashimi Raw yesterday.
You went to Sushi Lo?
I like Sushi Lo.
It's delicious.
They're all fish.
Oh, my God, everyone.
Everyone is a fish.
Everyone's a fish now.
No one knew what the right answer was.
"Oh, I'm going to get in the pool," he said.
I'm going in. You can go in.
Lightbourg.
Every day.
What?
She went to Disney with her long-distance boyfriend.
I love Disney.
I want to go to Disney.
I haven't been to Disney at all.
I want to go.
I ate a lot of raw oysters.
I ate 20 oysters.
What? When?
Recently?
A week's worth.
What?
That's a lot.
Twenty.
I make cakes every day.
Do you eat them every day?
Every day.
That's amazing.
What's Remote Disney?
What? Tell me. Tell me.
What's that?
Tell me.
And we're always willing to go.And we'd like to go there anytime too.
I ate beef tongue.
It's good. It's good.
They're selling eclairs.
You're lying.
I'm going to nibble on some whipped cream.
I'll nibble.
It'll come out if you open it before you nibble.
Fresh cream.
You don't have to serve it.
What an eclair.
Sure, sure.
I made hamburgers.
I made pickled plums.
What?
You made plums?
What do you mean plums?
How do you do plums?
Dried plums?
Yes.
You dip them in syrup?
Yes, yes.
The syrup would be more like dried plums.
You use it for hoss?
You can do it just by putting it on first.
You can put it on first.
I loved the shiso in the umeboshi.
I love it.
My mouth is getting really clammy.
My mouth.
Congratulations!
My mouth is getting tight.
I don't know if I can do it.
It's interesting, isn't it? Everyone.
It's funny. Everyone.
Kashigaki-san, too.
Go to the corner already.
Sakuragi-san, too.
You're funny.
Gayama-san, too.
Next, I would like to do this kind of project today.
What is it?
It's called, "The Funny and Fufu Familain Quiz!
We, EBITCHU, are going to be in the 6th and 7th of this weekend.
Ebichu Summer Familain Eisaku
Famien e Yamanagako 2022 will be held on the 6th and 7th of this weekend.
at the Yamanagako Exchange Plaza Kirara Theater Hibiki.
Yes.
Tickets are on sale now.
What are you doing? Alone.
Get it together.
What is Familien?
In a word, what is Famien?
It is an annual outdoor summer concert.
It's a summer outdoor concert.
This year, it will be the first time in 3 years since 2019,
This will be the first time for us to participate from here.
Yes, it's my first time. I'm going to participate.
So, what do you think this year's Famien will be like?
This year's Famien.
I can already see it, so why don't you just drink it?
I'm sure they'll find out that we've run away like this.
The three of us are dancing together, you know.
I thought they probably wanted to drink,
I thought it was probably coming down to us.
I tried to escape for a moment, but I couldn't escape at all.
It was a bit funny.
This year's Famien.
Yes, this year. This year, too.
Familiens always drink a lot of water.
Drinking water.
I wonder why they use so much water.
The amount of water seems to increase every year.
It's amazing.
This year, the village of Wootan.
Everyone loves it.
Wootan Village.
You can enjoy it even before the concert starts.
You can eat food.
And you can eat the food that everyone has requested.
What did you request?
I requested something like tri-colored gelato,
This is my first time at Famien,
So I got a gelato with those colors.
That's good. I'm sure it's delicious.
What about you, Hirata?
I did about three,
I only remember two.
What were they?
Grilled corn,
and a chocolate banana.
Oh, the regular shirt.
What was it again? I think it was a hot dog.
It was a hot dog.
Of course it was.
You eat a lot, don't you? I do.
In summer, it's hot dogs.
Hot dogs?
Hot dogs are delicious.Hot dogs are delicious.
They're delicious.
Isn't it good already, Riko?
I'll have one with cucumber asa-tsuke.
I didn't realize everyone had such a request,
Everyone else had two or so, but I only had one.
It's not right.
When they asked me to send it to them,
I was told to send one, and if it wasn't good enough, I was told to send two or three,
You can send two or three.
I definitely did.
Cucumbers didn't work?
What was wrong?
It was only cucumbers.
You asked me to send a couple of cucumbers, right?
Oh, yeah.
He's going to eat 12 cucumbers.
Hang in there! Don't get an upset stomach. It was a long time ago.
Oh, yeah. There's protein, right?
Yes. Before.
Right. I'm looking forward to it. That's why.
I'm looking forward to the concert, too.
I hope you all enjoy the singing village, too.
The other day, after we finished rehearsals, I thought my head was going to explode,
I really thought my head was going somewhere.
There is so much to learn.
The schedule was very tight this time,
It was a little tough.
I think it's great that Fanny overcame it.
I'm really proud of her.
Fanny?
It's us.
I thought it was great to be young.
Do you have any enthusiasm? It was our first time to play Fanny.
Rehearsals were pretty tough,
But I overcame that period,
I think my physical strength was also a failure in these two days,
I hope to give a good performance,
I will do my best.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I am the ninth Famien.
Please be well.
And this year's Famien,
This year's Famien is the first Famien for Coconner.
So I'm sure there are still a lot of things you don't know,
I would like to give you a quiz to prepare for the Famien,
I would like to give you a quiz to prepare you for the Famien.
For example, Famien should be completely hydrated.
is ○ or ×.
×x.
Which is ○ or ×?
Kaan.
It's either a circle or a kernel, everyone.
×It's not "X".
It's this way.
X or Y?
This way.
Oh, it's an X.
Correct.
What is it?
What was that?
I don't know.
I don't know what Riko is doing.
One more time.
Suddenly it's right.
I guess it's a circle.
Which is it?
Which is it? Which is it?
One more time.
Families should stay hydrated.
Is that a circle or an X?
XX.
Correct.
Good. Drink water, everyone.
Yes, and one more question.
For the last part of the Famien, all the members jumped into Yamada Coco.
Which is it?
X.
Correct.
Really?
No way.
I'm glad.
I'm happy.
You're happy?
I'm so happy.
Let's hold hands and dive in.
That's what I thought,
I've summarized it, in case you're interested.
I summarized it for you, didn't I?
Yes, I did.
Please send me quizzes like this in the comments.
As a veteran of Tamien, please answer correctly.
Veteran of Tamien.A veteran of Tamien.
You are out there every year.
I've been doing this since 2013.
Everyone, comment away.
Here they come.
Which is it?
Because I don't spill shaved ice on my costume.
Correct.
Did anyone spill shaved ice? In fact, yes.
Yes, I have.
I'm sorry.
Yes, there are.
During the concert.
I spilled it as soon as I changed.
When?
Maybe in 2013?
13 or 14?
That's right.
I spilled a strawberry or something on 13. On the white costume.
What?
I got mad at him afterwards.
Did you get scolded?
Yes, I did. I got scolded.
Let's not spill it.
Can we eat it this year?
I want to eat!
I haven't eaten on stage in a long time. I haven't had shaved ice on stage in a long time.
Hey!
What do you think?
For those of you who are attending Famie for the first time, please take a look at this to learn a little bit about it.
Famie has a mascot character. Which is it?
Correct answer!
But if you ask me to name these, I, for one, can't answer anything.
There are about six of them.
Oh, I see.
Something like Maruyoshi.
Marukichi? There is no such a thing.
What is it?
Koromaru?
Koromaru? !
Koromaru or Korokichi.
I was in charge of Kabo-chan.
I always say it every year in the script.
What was it again? Oh my God, Ebi, Ebi, Ebi Sawachan?
Wasn't there a shrimp? There was a shrimp, wasn't there?
Shrimp Maruko.
Look! Shrimps!
Oh, my gosh, you guys.
Look, look.
Ebi goro.
There it is. There it is.
Koromi.
That's great.
Have you seen something like a koroe?
There's Ryoji and others.
Who?
Who? Who?
Who is it, Mr. Ryouji?
Who is it?
There's no Mr. Ryouji.
Ebigoro, Koromaru, Koromi, Korozou, Koroe.
Korokitty.
That's great.
Ryouji is here.
Is there anyone on the staff?
No, he's not here.
No, I don't think so.
Is there anyone?
There might be.
Shall we introduce Mr. Ryoji as a character this year?
I wonder who he is.
It would be interesting.
Marukawa Suka, who is a famien until he goes home.
Maru.
That's correct.
Ryoji-kun was told to be the chairman of the board.
This is Fujisawa-san.
Fujisawa-san, huh?
I'm sorry.
But you know what? Ryoji said he's coming to Famien.
It's true.
He got mad at me for asking you to come, Ryoji.
I'm scared.
Ryoji.
Follow me.
Go on.
The maximum amount of snacks you can bring is 300 yen.
Which is it?
Heart?
Hearts?
Three or this.
I'll take March and a "B".
I'll take that one.
What's that, 300 yen?Wasn't it 300 yen?
I thought it was 500 yen.
It's 500 yen.
Was it? That's the rule.
No, it's not.
It's just something we were joking about.
Yes, it was.
How much was it? 500 yen or 1,000 yen?
It's 500 yen or 1,000 yen. 300 yen is not enough.
300 yen is not enough.
It was 1,000 yen.
What? No?
I can't even buy a photo.
That's true.
You can't buy anything.
You can't buy any merchandise.
Oh, it's 500 yen including tax.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
I don't get it.
500 yen.
It's okay.
Anything?
Because we all want to eat, don't we? In Utamura.
Yes, we do.
Do you have bananas for a snack?
You bought some!
I think you should buy what you want to buy.
That's right.
I've got an inside track on merchandise this year.
Yes!
That's right!
That's great.
Anything else?
Is there anything else...
Is there anything else, ladies and gentlemen?
There's a song we always perform every year!
At the God's Performance.
Maybe.
Yes, it's Maru.
What's in it?
Is it a good yu?
Oh.
I want to enroll.
But I think they're doing it.
I don't know if they're doing it.
I don't know.
No, I'm sure she's doing it.
She's doing it.
I'm sure she's doing it.
Because this is the only place she does it.
Once a year.
It's the only place I do it once a year.
I like Iyuna, though.
Yes, I like it.
You know, with the view of Wada Kako and so on.
But there will be at least a break.
There's an eight-minute break.
Marukawazuka playing with water guns before the show starts.
Let's see, I want to play with this.
Someone wants to play.
It was a triangle.
I guess this is also a triangle.
In the past, we wanted to play.
It's getting a little bit tough, you know.
Well, after the summer season, we wanted to have a barbecue.
Fuji was registered as a World Heritage site,
Fuji was registered as a World Heritage site, so I have to take good care of Mt.
Also, before the concert, after rehearsal and before the concert,
There were members who played with water guns after rehearsal and before the show,
It's like they don't play with water guns anymore,
When I went out for a while,
I got wet when I went out for a bit,
I was a little bit pissed off.
That's true.
Well, there are many things.
But, you know, there is always a time when you can see a beautiful view from the stage,
Fuji?
When the weather is nice.
Yes, yes.
That's right.
By the climbers,
But you can't see them,
But the climbers can see us?
Lights, lights.
Sometimes they can see us, right?
That's right. It's dark when you're climbing.
Evening light.
So, you know, when you climb Mt.
Fuji. You can't see people, but the light is like this.
That's right.
It's that close.
It's not that close,
It's not that close, but..,
But sometimes you can see them.
It's amazing.
The light.
Did you see it today? Coconner, all kinds of things.
Yes, I did.I understand.
Suddenly.
I mean, let's have fun, right?
Families have fun, too.
I'll tell you this, and change your clothes, too.
Yes, yes.
You might want to bring it.
There is a big chance you will get wet, or rather, you will get wet.
It will get wet. I think there will be a lot of water.
Yes, it is.
There are two days, but the first day is in the evening, and it gets cold after dark,
So there is a temperature difference.
The next day might be hot,
From 12:30 p.m.
It's my first time. Family Rain.
From noon.
Right.
Usually we have two days in the evening,
This time we're going to do it in the evening.
Please be aware of global warming,
Even if you think it's hot, you might want to wear a light jacket.
I think it would be better to bring one.
I think it would be better to bring it with you.
Also, I am a little sorry to say that the area where people can speak out is no longer allowed,
I'm sorry to say that the area where people are allowed to speak out has become NG due to the spread of the infection.
I can't speak out,
I hope everyone can make memories of summer together at Familain,
Please shout loudly in your hearts,
I hope you will shout loudly in your hearts, and enjoy the choreography and hands together.
I hope you can enjoy it together.
It's coming soon, everyone.
That's right. The show will start in three days.
I know you're all waiting for it.
Please look forward to it, everyone.
Please do.
Well then, that's all for now, the delightful and huffy Familain Quiz.
Yes, I'll be back soon.
Yes!
Yes, it's the end of the 48th edition of B-China's Delightful and Funny Showroom.
That was fast!
Yes. Let's make an announcement here.
Yes! It's early.
What's with the hearts, aren't the hearts really thick?
What is this?
What is that? I'm only talking about the "kokonari".
Wait a minute. Where is it? Which one?
The announcement course. There's a lot of them.
Not this one?
Yes. It's just as I just told you,
B. Summer Family Production of Yamanakako, or Familain Yamanakako 2022 for short, will be held on Saturday, August 6 and Sunday, August 7 at the Kirara Theater attached to the Yamanakako Exchange Plaza Kirara Theater.
The event will open at 3:00 p.m. and start at 4:30 p.m. on August 6 and at 11:00 a.m. and 12:30 p.m. on August 7.
Let's have a lot of fun and make summer memories together.
And now..,
We Sing A Popular Tune On The Stage 1st Tune On 2022 will be held on Saturday, September 24th and Sunday, September 25th.
Both days will be held in two parts, opening at 12:00 pm, starting at 1:00 pm, and opening at 4:00 pm, starting at 5:00 pm.
The venue will be the outdoor stage at Chichibu Muse Park in Saitama Prefecture.
Tickets will go on sale on Saturday, August 27th at 10:00.
What will they sing at this year's event? We hope you can look forward to it.
And here it is,
This is Coco's.
Sakuragi's birthday?
Sakuragi's solo live Sakuragi Night Prom New Opening will be held on Friday, September 16, 2022.
It will be held at M's THE GARDEN HALL in Tokyo on Friday, September 16, 2022, opening at 18:00 and starting at 19:00.
General sales will start on Saturday, August 20 at 10:00am.
Please come.
Everyone was looking forward to our first concert.
Sakuragi Gundan.
We called ourselves Sakuragi Gundan.
Or the name of the fans.
Sakuragi Gundan, please come and play with us.
It's going to be fun.
And lastly, Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku's 10th ANNIVERSARY album "Nakayoshi" was announced the other day.
It will be released on Wednesday, September 21, 2022.
It has songs from the past and some re-recorded by the 9 members,
The bonus Blu-ray includes a documentary that traces the 10-year history of Ebichu,
It will be interesting to see what kind of things will be included in the Blu-ray,
Nakayoshi, I hope you are looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
So, here is the final ranking, the Top 5.
Top 5.
The fifth place goes to Mr. Shackelford.
Thank you very much.
In 4th place, Mr. Po-chan Ewa.
In 3rd place, Mr. Enruu.
2nd place, Maa-san.
Thank you very much.
First place, Yukitsun-san.
Yes. So, that's the end of the 48th edition of EBICHU's Delightful and Full Showroom.
Yes, and the next installment will be coming soon. And we will announce the next distribution at a later date.
This distribution will also be supported by the reflection meeting that will take place after this, so please check it out.
The distribution will end once, but it will resume in a bit, so please stay tuned.
If you have anything you would like to share with us in the reflection session, please comment.
That's all for now, this is the new Bicucate.
Bye-bye.
I'm going to be late for my age.
He said, "Hucka, you're amazing.
It's early. It's already started.It's too early. It's already started.
It started.
It's early.
Thank you for your hard work.
Mr. Nakayama, how was your first expression in January?
It's been half a year.
It's been six months.
Your mouth didn't listen to me.
It was out of control, on the way.
It was perfect.
It's been a long time since I've MC'd.
Weren't you the MC in January?
I don't think so.
It's been over a year.
I see.
Have you been growing?
It's been going downhill.
That's no good.
It was fun.
Did you understand a lot about the work?
I understood a lot.
Yes, I did.
Mosmos.
I can't do this anymore, here.
It's important.
It's not that frustrating.
More and more mosmos.
Mosmos.
I'm looking forward to more Mosmos.
I have nothing left but bosses.
It's wonderful.
Mosmos for everyone.
I said it clearly, twice.
You said it twice, clearly.
Mosmos.
It was a mamim memo.
If I made a mistake once, I would understand.
Mosmos is already.
It's funny.
It says "Samantha Mosmos.
It's Kao's, right?
Mosmos.
Well then, please end on a good note for the Famie, Mr. Nakamura.
Ah.
The FAMIE will be held on August 6 and 7.
Maru!
Correct!
Everyone, please stay hydrated, it's been 3 years since the last FAMIE.
Let's have a fun summer with M2!
I can't tell which camera is which.
I'm sure.
There have been so many things all along.
Isn't this it? This is it!
Oh, no. It's a pull camera.
It says "pull camera" on it.
Let's have fun!
It says here, you see?
When none of the red lights are lit, it says this camera is in use.
Wow, it's true!
I am!
All of you!
It's me!
Let's have fun!
See you soon!
Bye bye!
That's all for today's video!
Thank you for watching to the end!
See you next time!